

#### **CONTACT ME AT**

- Jl. Diponegoro 3/18, Cepu Blora, Central Java, Indonesia
- lintanghannan123@gmail.com
- +6282136640652
- in @lintanghannanmaulana

### SKILLS SUMMARY

Lab Assistant

Front-End Skills: HTML, CSS, and Javascript

IoT Developer

**Technical Support** 

Process Improvement

#### LICENSE AND CERTIFICATES

- Belajar Dasar Pemrograman Web, Dicoding, Feb 2021 - Feb 2024
- Google IT Support Specialization, Coursera, Mar 2021
- Google IT Automation with Python Specialization, Coursera, Mar 2021
- Architecting with Google Compute Engine Specialization, Coursera, May 2021

# LINTANG HANNAN MAULANA

# JUNIOR FRONT-END

#### SUMMARY

I graduated from Cloud Computing at Bangkit Indonesia 2021. The contributions i have made while working at Capstone has given me a wealth of experience on how to teach groups, take responsibility, for assigned projects, and manage under-membered groups in capstone work. Now I am still studies at Telkom University and actively in the Laboratory as Practicum Assistant. Furthermore, I am very responsible for what has been entrusted to me and a conscientious person who work hard.

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

## **Cloud Computing Student**

Bangkit Indonesia 2021 | Feb 2021 - Jul 2021

- Collaborate with a team to create a project or capstone using Machine learning combined with a web application and deploy it to the public
- Work closely with a team or partner to communicate solving problems about the program and create strategies to solve them
- Learn and compare the various compute and storage services available on the Google Cloud Platform, including Google App Engine, Google Compute Engine, Google Kubernetes, Google Cloud Storage, Google Container Registry, Google Cloud Run, Google Cloud SQL and BigQuery

#### **Practicum Assistant**

Cyber Physical Security Laboratory | May 2021 - Current

- Work with the team to make learning modules according to the curriculum
- Providing teaching to students
- Work with a team to manage the laboratory's LMS (Learning Management System) site

# EDUCATIONAL HISTORY

# Telkom University

Telecommunication Engineering | Aug 2018 - Current

 Still studies at Telkom University as student and actively organizing in Cyber Physical Security Laboratory Telkom University

## Bangkit 2021

Cloud Computing | Feb 2021 - Jul 2021

- Score: 92.94
- Attendance Percentage: 97.22%
- Graduated from Cloud Computing path in Google Bangkit Indonesia 2021 and active in working with groups or partners to discuss problems experienced and complete projects